(Sheldon:)Pervert.
Have you thought about why Arthur
didn't want you to read his paper?
(Sheldon:)Yes, I have.
(Sheldon:)And my only conclusion is the
prescription he was picking up
(Sheldon:)the other day was for cuckoo pills.
Maybe he found you a bit much.
(Sheldon:)That's kind of a stretch.
(Sheldon:)Look, when it comes to social skills,
I've mastered the big three.
(Sheldon:)There's the coy smile.
(Sheldon:)There's the friendly chuckle.
(Sheldon:)There's the vocalization of sympathy.
Aww...
(Sheldon:)That last one's tricky.
I'm still working on it.
(Amy:)From what I saw the other day,
(Amy:)I could understand why he and...
(Amy:)Some people might find you...
(Howard:)What?
(Amy:)Doesn't matter.